this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to become the
next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture the
unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world after being separated from his crew
luffy set out to rescue his captured brother ace to do so he snuck into the government prison
impelled down after his rescue attempt failed luffy and a number of prisoners rushed to escape
only to encounter blackbeard one of the seven warlords of the sea
i'm saving this i'll find a way i ain't gonna stop you kid you give it your best nothing's
impossible in this world after all but i've already told you that remember sky island
and just like sky island the one piece is really out there
i can't wait for you to see what we've got in store trust me you're gonna be impressed
in a few hours we're gonna put on a show so explosive that'll shake the whole damn world
ignore him luffy come on
keep moving boys straight to level three
i've got a funny feeling you're magellan and i'm guessing you're blackbeard
hit the nail right on the head pal
let me drop
what is this stuff
straw hat how the hell could you possibly survive after i poisoned you
there's no doubt that he's the one who caused all this mayhem
the next chance i get nothing will stop me from taking his life
the poison guy
i promise you this straw hat you will never escape this prison
stop the jelly eva's esoteric technique explodes
keep running trust me you don't want to look back
you can't escape from me
let's hurry
that was the last group
everyone else who was behind them is no longer standing they didn't make it
awesome
clap
last
Inazuma!
Ready to go.
Great scissors.
Wait, why'd you just cut the staircase?
Eva hasn't come up yet.
All you need to worry about is getting out of here.
Eva.
I'll do as you said.
Members of the Air Force.
Who canности do the air off or have you ever seen?
Me!
Liverpool!
方面 of the Air Force!
To food.
I don't know.
This is suicide.
What are you hoping to accomplish?
Curious, are we?
If you can't figure it out,
you must be terribly slow.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What I meant to say...
Is that you're stupid!
Death wing!
Yee-haw!
So how many of those heads have you got to show me?
Even if you do buy yourself some time,
Straw Hat and his little friends still have no means of escape.
Buy some time?
Goodness!
How cheeky!
Already convinced you can beat me, are you?
Kamabaka style!
New Kamakenpo!
Feast your eyes on this, drippy boy!
Kamabaka!
Hee-haw!
What's wrong?
You scared?
Come here!
Hee-haw!
A-ha!
Bang on the max!
Zhu-maze!
Jumaze!
Hey, something's weird!
Where's the poison guy?
He was right behind him!
I'm sure it's no coincidence that Eva and Inazuma stopped in the lower level!
What?
They stayed behind to find that poison guy by themselves?
We need to help them!
Let's go back!
Are you pulling my tail?!
They don't call him a miracle worker for nothing!
If he thinks he can handle the big boss, then be grateful and keep moving!
Ralphs and Ralphs again!
There's something fishy going on!
We're getting through here way too easy!
Indeed!
I was thinking the same thing!
Also, I don't see any prisoners in the cells!
And all of the doors are wide open!
Someone must have come through and released them!
But why?
Move it, boys!
Freedom's waiting for you!
Thanks, Captain Boogie!
Woohoo!
Yes, I can't believe it!
I'm out!
Have a weapon and do your part!
Here you go!
Thanks!
Take this!
Quick!
Fire!
Let's go!
To the top!
Speaker 8
Let's go!
One-
Go to the top!
After a stroke of luck allowed them to escape from level two,
which had been blocked by Magellan's poison,
Captain Buggy, Mr. Three, and the others
are closing in on the main entrance.
They are now on level one.
Led by Luffy, the mob of newcomers
and the prisoners they freed continue their ascent
through Impel Down.
Running through level four and three,
they've now made their way to level two,
the wild beast hell,
where they found surprisingly little resistance.
Meanwhile, Ivankov has put a temporary halt
through Warden Magellan's poisonous pursuit
by doing battle with him on level three.
My spine, it hurts so much.
Damn you, Ivankov.
Unforgivable.
I'm gonna get out of here.
Get out of here!
After them!
Earn your feet!
Or I'm gonna smash them!
I'm beating out of you!
Despite their repeated defeats,
Sadie has used her unique brand of motivation
to coax the demon guards into another battle on level one.
Jail manager Shiryu, who is now running wild,
cut all lines of communication with the outside world
so that no one could discover the situation within the prison.
And so, the unprecedented events happen one after another,
literally behind closed doors.
Fortunately for us, Impel Down is surrounded by prison ships and Navy ships.
If we could somehow manage to steal one of them,
we could use it to get to Marineford before Ace's execution.
Works for me!
Hold on, Ace, we're coming for you!
Only four hours remain until Ace's public execution at Navy Headquarters.
Ah! Hee-haw!
Oh, my mate!
I can feel it melting away!
Oh, the pain!
The agony!
Oh, my beautiful face!
You monster!
Ah!
Oh, it's going to...
Melt!
Or not.
Ha!
My makeup protected me.
It's not going to melt!
Hee-haw!
You shuffle-ed me.
Ha-ha-ha!
Hee-haw!
Ha-ha!
Heeehaw!
Death, wink, wink!
Death, wink, wink, wink!
Wink, wink, wink!
Whink, wink, wink!
Wings! Wings! Wings! Wings! Wings! Wings!
Venom Blowfish!
Push!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Why in a time like this, my boot laces?
They came loose, came loose, came loose!
Or maybe not, because these beauties are laceless!
Hee-haw!
There's no laces?
You got me there!
Hee-haw!
This is foolish.
There's nothing to gain by stalling for time.
Think so?
Oh, but I'm having so much fun doing it.
Fine, then, have it your way.
You want to end this?
How about right now?
New Kama Kenpo 44 aesthetic technique.
Hair removal fist!
They're liberal fist!
ha-dah sound-
He's still alive.
Let him roll.
Eva.
Oh, no.
Now, came out!
You're trying to stall me, too.
The four demon guards are at once!
We're screwed!
It's all over!
Come back to yourselves!
You can't fight them!
The whole freaking up thing is cancelled, okay?
Come on!
Let's pull it together!
Bastard!
What are you trying to...
Holy crap!
F-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-foss!
Oh?
Oh!
It's been a while, Mr. Three.
I see you're a whimpering imbecile just like before.
Eh, who in their right mind would release this pain in the butt?
C...Cap...Captain Buggy!
Huh?
Look! Those guys knocked out all four Demon Guards!
What?
Straw hats!
And that's the Warlord Team Bay!
There you are!
God, I'm glad you guys are okay!
He is too much!
Oh, it just breaks my heart!
Captain Buggy, look!
There are a bunch of released prisoners and perverts
that are coming up one after another from level two!
Perverts do? What the hell?
Who are you calling perverts?
This is what you two goons get for walking out on us back there!
Thanks a lot!
What are you doing Captain Buggy?
This is bad! Those prisoners are from level four!
And they made it all the way up here!
How'd they get away from Warden Magellan?
Damn it! Two riots happened at the same time under our watch!
Where's the warden now?
So who's that guy?
Hydra!
Atilla is here too? What is happening on this floor?
Crap, something bad happened to Eva and the crab guy!
Atilla is here too!? What is happening on this floor!?
A Crap, something bad happened to Eva and the crab guy!?
Agile is here too? What is happening on this floor?
Crap! Something bad happened to Eva and the crab guy!
Huh?
Despite Ivankov's efforts, Magellan catches up to the escaped prisoners.
Luffy and Mr. Three form an unlikely team to slow him down one final time.
However, when Jinbei and the others reach the top of the prison at last,
they find that the Warden has a very ugly surprise waiting for him.
On the next, One Piece! Magellan's tricky move! A foiled escape plan!
I'm the King of the Pirates!